Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Hey. Dad. Dad.
Hey. what's up?
Sheppard's falling behind again.
He's exhausted. showed up late.
putting the rest of the guys
in danger.
- Well. his brother's sick.
- He's a good kid. but one man
doesn't take precedent
over the team.
Let me talk to him.
I'm gonna have to let him go.
Dad. you just said so yourself.
he's a good kid.
Come on.
just let me talk to him.
Go get your tools.
I'll meet you in the truck.
Ah! Dad!
- Eric?
- Please! Please! Help me! Dad!
Eric! Eric!
- Dad! Dad!
- What the fuck?
I got you. I got you.
Dad! Please. Dad. Dad.
Dad!
Please. please. help me. Dad.
- Dad!
- Eric!
Eric.
Eric!
Dad!
Hello. Arianne.
It's Darren Atkins again.
The team and I
are all set for the trip.
our gear is ready.
and we packed
as light as possible.
so we're only bringing
essential equipment.
Okay.
I'm excited to get going.
and looking forward
to meeting you in person.
Thank you.
Are we close?
- All right. excuse me. What?
- Come on. man.
- let the woman drive.
- I'm letting her drive.
We exited the freeway
four hours ago.
Okay. none of these roads
are on the maps.
We don't have any signal.
I just...
Want to continually attack
her professionalism.
Well?
Is there anything I could do
to maybe facilitate
your driving?
You could shut up. amigo.
Okay. Hey. look. this isn't
meant to be a criticism.
but how do you know
where we're going?
I was raised by wolves.
Sarcasm is gonna get us there
quicker.
You know. I'm curious.
Arianne.
how many of the expeditions
you've aided
have had
a scientific objective?
With all due respect. sir.
I don't discuss my clients
with other clients.
I hope you'll consider that
an asset.
Yes. of course.
Although I hope
that this will be an expedition
we will all want to talk about
for years to come.
I'm just here to get you
to where you need to go.
Fair enough.
This looks promising.
Maybe we can get a postcard.
I'm getting hungry.
Anyone else getting hungry?
Wait here. I won't be long.
Copy.
You okay?
All right.
Excuse me. sir.
I'd like to buy some water
for the five of us
and some coolant for the car.
if you have it?
Also.
I'm looking for directions.
We've been tracking the river
for a couple of hours
past Peaks Mill. South Pike.
But I can't seem to find
where I need to go.
Where'd that be?
Shookum Hills.
I ain't never heard of it.
Old mountain town.
used to be around here
until it burned down
to the ground.
back in the '70s.
I'm working off an atlas
from 1972 out there.
and on any map after that
it seems like the town
was literally
wiped off the face of the earth.
Any help you could offer
will be much appreciated.
You go back
the way you came.
You'll reach the freeway.
Stay on that
till you get back to your city.
You'll be fine.
Great.
Thanks.
Dale. We've got a problem.
So?
We're close.
- Let's go.
- All right.
Well it's about time.
Did they have any food in there?
We should go back.
What's that. Shawn?
It's not here.
Let's go back.
The fact it's not
here is the reason we are.
We shouldn't be here.
Right.
Right. we should go back.
We should throw two years
- of research...
- Hang on.
What are you doing?
- Hey!
- Jesus! What the fuck!
We're not alone.
- Friendly escort?
- Not likely.
Hold on.
Hey. slow down.
- Come on. slow down!
- Hang on.
No. I'm serious.
slow the fuck down!
Can you lose them?
- I'm being serious.
- Relax.
- We're going too fast.
- Slow down!
She's got this.
Nice driving. Arianne.
Are you trying
to get us killed?
Doing what I'm paid to do.
You paying her
to get us killed?
It's fine. she knows
what she's doing. all right?
There you go.
What was that?
That was an escort.
They wanted to push us past one
very specific point in the road.
All right.
so what are you saying?
That spot where he slowed down.
that's where we need to go.
It should be close.
Look for openings
and sidetracks.
Guys. look.
Up there to the right.
This is it.
Stop. Don't touch it.
It's electrified.
All right.
Darren.
Why put up an electric fence
in the middle of nowhere?
They want to keep us out.
This doesn't feel right.
We need to find
our way around this gate.
Those branches
are too thin to climb.
Or your ass is too big.
Really. man?
Six percent body fat.
Yeah. right.
How do you know that?
Hey. Arianne?
Let's go.
This is a good spot. guys.
So. what do we have
to worry about out here?
Is this shit like quicksand
or what?
A sinkhole...
is formed when
an underground cavity collapses.
They've been known
to swallow livestock.
people. cars. even houses.
Many were formed by coal seams
that catch fire
and collapse
as the coal smolders.
- So that's what happened here?
- No. we don't know yet.
There are hundreds
of coal seam fires
throughout the world.
Some were ignited
through natural processes.
Others were brought on by men
in mining accidents.
And then
there's Shookum Hills.
We know there was a fire.
but not what caused it.
We know there was a town here.
not why it vanished.
- And we know there were miners.
- If they were miners.
And I'm out.
- Really?
- What do you mean if?
Here we go.
Well. the prevailing theory
is that this was never
actually a coal mine.
but America's response
to the Well to Hell.
The Kola Borehole
in Siberia.
The Russians
decided to drill
the deepest borehole
in the world
- and they did. supposedly.
- Okay.
They dug 8 miles
straight down
until the drill broke.
Then they lowered
a heat resistant microphone
into the well
where they recorded this sound.
What the hell was that?
Some say
it's the screams of the damned.
Echoes. distorted echoes
of slight underground grinding
of tectonic plates.
happens everywhere lithosphere
is disrupted by mining.
A natural reaction
to a natural invasive procedure.
So the theory
is the American government
decided to drill their own well
here at Shookum Hills.
And now everyone is gone.
The whole place is gone.
Right. so. what you really need
to worry about
is not whether this shit
is like quicksand.
but rather that key members
of this expedition
continue to discard fundamental
scientific principles
and throw all reason
out the window.
I am not discarding science.
- Oh. no?
- I am just trying
to embrace the notion
that folklore. myth.
religion
all stem from a merger
between science
and. you know.
actual human experience.
That idea might have grown
from a combination
of myth and fact.
- Yeah.
- Just like intelligent design
is not a concept
that disregards the big bang.
It just keeps us open
to the possibility
that God created it.
Except he didn't. Shawn.
A rapid disruption
of the primordial singularity
did 15 billion years ago.
- So you say.
- So science says.
Christ. what is this?
Sophomore philosophy class?
Christ.
Also. real guy. myth. both?
- Mom and Dad are fighting again.
- They need counseling.
I'm not having
this conversation.
You seem to know what happened.
tell us.
It's obvious.
an environmental disaster.
And we're not here
to find hell.
We're here
to find holes and smoke.
Hmm. So basically hell. then.
Thank you. guys. very much
for clearing that up.
I'm sorry I asked.
How long?
I don't know.
Did someone cut the wire?
Not cut.
It's torn.
What? Like a fucking animal
chew on it or something?
I don't think so.
It's been pulled.
Stripped from inside.
At least the grating held.
What's the voltage?
Apparently not enough.
Cain.
they're trying to get out. Check your zone.
Yes. ma'am. I'm on it.
Closing in on to 16 and 18.
I'll check in when I'm done.
Over.
I hear you. devil.
That's my knife.
Okay.
Just don't like anyone else
- touching it.
- I get it.
I feel the same way
about my PlayStation.
No. you don't.
- Have a good night.
- Good night.
Hey. hey.
Hey.
So. Darren.
Yeah?
Where did you find her?
A colleague of mine.
he did a dig with her
in Tanzania.
Worst personality ever.
he said.
Arrogant. self-absorbed.
But she got him
where he needed to go.
She worked in Africa. huh?
Yeah. all over the
world. apparently.
She likes to travel.
Yep.
Or she doesn't wanna
go home.
Hmm.
Did you tell him?
I didn't need to.
Any sign of those kids?
Couldn't find them.
But I scared them good.
We're fine.
I want them gone.
no matter what it takes.
Are we clear?
Can you fix this?
I can patch it up.
But I don't know
if it'd hold.
Arianne. Hello?
I just wanted to thank you.
For what?
Well. for getting us
this far.
Pay me first.
thank me later.
You know. I was thinking.
We could use your help
in the mine.
if you care to join.
I'm not a scientist.
My responsibility
is to get you there as agreed.
Then I'm done.
Okay. but what's next for you
after this?
I've got another gig.
What. more exciting
than being part
of a groundbreaking
scientific discovery?
I don't discuss
my clients with...
Right. yes.
with other clients. right.
Where did you scoop up
that group
of super hombres out there?
What's that?
That group of men you have.
Terry's an old acquaintance.
He's not much of a talker.
But he knows his tech
and can power up
pretty much anything with
a stick and a piece of string.
Shawn is...
We share the same fascination
for this place. really.
And as annoying as he is.
he's an expert geologist.
He has my respect.
Jaime's pretty new.
He joined us about a month ago.
Security services.
Why do you need
private security
for a scientific expedition?
Well. to keep us safe.
Safe from what?
Um...
I like to be prepared.
What are you expecting
to find here?
Anthracite.
Ultra high-grade.
It burns like nothing else.
If... If we can sample it.
find out exactly
how it smolders and spreads.
we might have a key
to understanding what causes
these environmental disasters
and prevent future ones.
And that's it? Nothing more?
A thousand people lived
in Shookum Hills. Arianne.
A thousand. all gone.
Even with a great fire
people don't just disappear
like that.
Towns don't.
Something else
happened here.
Something more.
And I'm here
to discover what that is.
document it
and bring it home.
So the truth. I guess. is...
what I'm hoping to find.
I'm sorry.
It's just my vitamins.
So. what... What do you think
we'll find here?
Only what you take with you.
Nietzsche. right?
Yoda.
Right.
Well. have a good night.
Good night.
Darren. This is what.
like the fifth one of these?
Yeah. it's probably
a warning system for gas leaks.
Looks pretty new.
Look at this.
Studio foam.
- What?
- Soundproofing.
What is that doing here?
Terry.
Yeah. I see it.
I smell sulfur. Be careful.
Yeah. I'll take out
the CO2 readers.
Check the BTUs.
Someone's coming. Get down.
Guys.
that's the car from yesterday.
Let's keep moving.
They know we're here.
- Hey. Terry?
- Yeah.
You can literally feel heat
from the fires.
Guys!
Come look at this!
We found it.
These buildings are
way older than I expected.
It makes sense.
This has been a mining town
since the early 1900s.
- I'm gonna document this.
- Yeah.
This looks
like some kind of shop.
Oh. look at this.
What's the air stat?
Slightly elevated.
but that's to be expected.
Nothing out of the green.
But as the mines burn.
they occasionally release
methane and carbon monoxide.
And this air monitor detects
them before we do.
Yeah.
we should probably get out of here.
It's our canary
in the coal mine as it were.
Now. as you can see.
entire shops and houses
were abandoned outright.
We've yet to determine
if the inhabitants left
because of the gases.
the sinkholes or something else.
So can I thank you now?
You surely can.
Shoot away. mate.
- I wonder how far down this goes?
- Well. let's find out.
Yeah. it's electrified.
Well. can we power it off
or something?
I don't know about powering off.
maybe bypass it.
Like that?
Yeah. something like that.
Get the scanner.
You can't get any closer.
He's fine.
We should secure you both
with a line.
This grate's unstable.
It's not safe.
I can't authorize this.
You're right. You can't.
Go on.
- Get the scanner.
- Yep. One second.
Hey. Shawn. Can you give me
a hand with this?
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Terry.
- Yeah?
- What is that?
Records image. sound.
measures air composition.
then distills and separates
each individual component
for subsequent analysis.
It checks for anthracite.
Got it.
All right. here we go.
Lower it. Shawn.
Okay. what do you got?
Nothing yet.
All right.
Lower it.
I hit the bottom.
Nothing?
No.
All right. here we go.
Hey. Shawn.
C15-H11-0.
The composition
is extremely pure.
I've never seen
anything like that.
That's it. man.
We've got it.
I've found it.
Shawn. bring up the scanner.
Hey. hold on. one second.
Wait. wait. wait.
There is something
down there.
What the hell is that?
Aah! Fuck!
- What happened?
- Goddamn it!
- What?
- It blew my ear drum out. man.
Turn it up. Listen to this.
Turn it up.
Listen.
Right there.
What is that?
- You hear it?
- Sort of.
Terry!
- Terry!
Help!
Help me!
- Can you hear us?
- We have to get him.
Terry!
Oh. no! Oh. no!
No! Help me!
Help me!
- What just happened?
- Jaime. get over here.
- Jaime!
- We shouldn't have been here.
We shouldn't be here.
Shawn.
I need the gas detector.
Shawn! The detector.
Darren!
We're going in after him. okay?
Just keep close
and follow my lead.
I got it.
Let's go.
Terry.
Terry!
Darren.
Hey!
I'll talk to him.
We need your help.
You need to call for help.
- What have you done?
- Our friends are down there.
What have you done?
Someone fell down the hole.
- How long has this been open?
- Our friends...
How long has this been open!
Sir. It's fine. It's fine.
Jaime. did you hear that?
Jaime.
Gas levels
are through the roof.
We have to get out of here.
I'm not leaving him
down here.
If we don't save ourselves.
everyone dies.
We have to go.
- Someone fell down the hole.
- You've got a rope.
- I'll cut it.
- No. No.
- No.
- Back the fuck up.
It's fine. sir.
You can't do that.
There's people down there.
Arianne. quick!
Jaime.
What's going on?
- Fuck.
- Let's go.
Oh. fuck.
- Is he dead?
- No. no.
- Did I kill him?
- No. he's fine.
He's fine. Shawn.
He's fine.
What happened? Who is this?
He tried to cut the rope.
Hey. hey.
- Call an ambulance.
- How? Our cells are no good here
and our satellite phone
was on Terry.
Where is he?
Where's Terry?
What happened to him?
- We couldn't find him.
- Fuck! Fuck this!
- What do you mean?
He didn't run away.
No. of course not.
So? What happened to him?
We don't know
what's down there.
Gas levels were sky-high.
We might be dealing
with something...
Something else.
- What was that thing?
- What thing?
- You saw. We all saw.
- I don't know
- what you're talking about.
- What do you mean?
- We need to leave now!
- Just leave him here?
The man came with a knife
and a shotgun.
I'm not waiting to see
what he pulls next.
Okay. we'll call for help
as soon as we reach a spot
where we can.
Now let's go. Please.
Guys. he's right. Let's go.
Come on. let's go.
I should have never allowed you
to convince me to come here.
You've been as obsessed
with this place as I have.
- But given your track record.
- Fuck off. Shawn.
Darren's received five warnings
for scientific misconduct
from three universities.
two kicked him out.
- What?
- Who do old thinkers expel
- from their midst?
- Psychopaths.
- Visionaries.
- Who is funding this again?
It isn't Cambridge
Earth Science Department.
Oh. shit.
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck!
This thing's not going anywhere.
It'll be dark soon.
We better reach the fence.
Let's go.
Fuck.
Oh. shit. Fuck.
This is Dale. Come in.
Gotcha. what's up?
We have a breach.
Repeat. We have a breach.
What the fuck is going on?
We triggered an alarm.
Through that. then west.
We should be back on track.
- Okay. There it is again.
- What? What is it?
- Listen.
- What is that?
There.
Turn off the flashlights.
Give me the night vision.
What is that?
Don't know. Same thing I heard
in the tunnel.
Where is it coming from?
Follow the light on my bag.
- Jaime. Stay close.
- What?
I hear something. over there.
Yeah. I hear it too.
Look out!
What the fuck was that?
Shawn!
Go. Go. move. Go!
Shit!
Everybody run.
Run!
Go. go. go!
Hey! Guys. a truck!
Let's go. now!
Hey!
Help us!
Hey. over here!
Get in the truck.
Now. quick!
Go. go. go!
Out of my way.
Move.
Wait here and keep quiet.
Where's Dale?
- I'm getting nothing.
- Get him on the radio.
Keep trying.
I knew it.
I knew you son of a bitches
were gonna cause trouble.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
My name is Darren Atkins.
Professor of Geology
at the Department
of Earth Sciences. Cambridge.
We're here
on purely academic purposes
to perform a series
of geological survey tests.
How did you find us?
Your guys
basically led us straight here.
We had a general sense
of the area.
You had a general sense
of the area?
Yes.
What does that mean?
A general sense of the area.
What did you just say?
How did you find us?
My father used
to track down people for money.
and I knew I had to look
for where someone
made an effort to hide a trail.
Where's your father now?
He lost his way.
Well. we've all lost something.
haven't we?
Schuttmann.
I can't reach Dale or Cain.
It could be out of range.
You're Paul Schuttmann?
Co-founder of Shookum Hills
mining company?
I used to be.
Now I do what you might call
security and protection work.
What is it you protect?
You.
What happened here?
What is this place?
A fucking hellhole.
That's what it is.
Everybody here has their
own beliefs about what this is.
What's yours?
Maybe it's purgatory.
The place where we go
to confront our sins.
where we're tested
on our flaws.
And you either come clean
or get destroyed.
My sin was greed.
What's yours?
Shelby. you there?
I'm here.
I got a couple of them.
scattered the rest.
There's a lot of them.
We've got a breach somewhere.
I don't know.
Find the breach.
I'll see what I can do here
and get back to you.
You opened a sinkhole?
- I suppose we...
- Which one!
I'll show you.
Look.
we lost a man down there.
Another one in the field.
Go with them. Find it.
- Seal it before it's too late.
- Let's go.
Move. asshole.
Professor.
- What are those?
- Keep up.
Why is this area
unprotected?
It's not.
We protect it.
We protect everybody.
Before y'all showed up.
we were doing a fine...
Nobody move.
They sounded us.
Hide.
Ellroy.
do you see anything out there?
Shelby. you copy?
Keep it down. What's up?
Stay in the safe house.
Whatever you do.
don't come out.
It's kind of too late
for that. Kip.
We made it to Safe House 4.
barely.
They're everywhere.
How many?
It's hard to say.
Never seen anything like it.
Fuck.
You've gotta get back inside.
Shel.
There's a house on the hill.
Do you think we can make it?
We don't know how many are out
there. We need to stay put.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- I can't run fast enough.
but I can slow them down.
- What?
- Find the breach and close it.
So give me this.
And the lighter.
Tell Dolores I didn't mess up
my good coat. All right?
Now. y'all
get the fuck out of here.
Go on. get.
Here I am. come get me!
Hey. you bastards!
Shit.
In there!
This is not good.
This isn't good.
There's one outside.
You have a rifle.
If anything comes in here.
you use it.
They are attracted to noise.
I don't see it anymore.
- Shelby. your status?
- Shit. Shit.
What is it doing?
Calling the others.
Listen carefully now.
No matter what you do.
don't let them grab you.
Because if they grab you.
they paralyze you
and they take you
down there.
God only knows what they
do to you when they've got you.
Go.
Okay.
Fuck!
Back up!
- I'm okay!
- There's an exit!
- Let's go!
- Come on! Go!
Keep moving.
There's a way through.
Hurry up. they're coming.
- This way.
- Wait.
Take these.
I'm gonna create
a diversion.
- I'll join you again later.
- But we need you.
Have a little faith.
What?
Go.
Come and get me.
you assholes!
- It's a dead end.
- In here.
- Come on.
- Yeah. right. Go.
Let's put up that grating.
It'll slow them down.
We gotta get it from outside.
Go. Go. hurry up.
Oh. shit. The grenade!
Give me the grenade!
- Jaime!
- Get down!
Darren.
Wait. Wait.
We've lost them.
Get up. We have to keep going.
They're all gone.
We don't know that.
What if
it doesn't kill them?
Just takes them away.
keeps them alive
somewhere down there?
What if...?
Darren.
I should have
never brought you.
I'm the one
who brought us here.
You know. Shawn was right.
We weren't financed
by the university.
I was backed
by a private mining company
who wanted this coal.
They offered me recognition
and a great deal of money.
That's why we're all here.
That's why they're all gone.
It's my fault.
I guess you were right.
About what we'd find here.
Truth.
My last tour with a repeat team
was a climb in the Himalayas.
One of them.
experienced climber.
fell off a cliff.
It was just the two of us
that day.
I had him.
but I couldn't get him up.
We waited for hours.
but no one came.
We would have both frozen
to death.
So in the end.
I cut the rope.
That's what you do
in situations like that.
But I won't leave you behind.
You have to come with me.
What's the fucking point?
I'm gonna get help.
Take this.
You'll be fine.
Stay here.
I will come back for you.
You're alive. thank God.
I tried to find you.
The grenade.
Can you grab it?
I can't move.
What is that?
An alternative species.
Shawn.
It's real.
They breed and colonize.
Like ants and bees.
If only the world could see.
If only... No.
Shawn.
Our Father. who art in
heaven. hollowed be thy...
Our Father...
The grenade.
Who art in heaven.
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come...
We gotta get out of here.
Put this on.
They're coming.
Climb. Climb.
Hurry! Darren. Hurry!
- No! No! Aah!
- Aah! No!
No! No!
Here. take my knife.
Kill it.
It's what you do. right?
In situations like this.
Wait. Don't!
Help me. Get me out of here.
Help me. Help me.
I'm sorry. I can't.
Please. They're coming.
Please!
I can't.
No man is more important...
Get her out of here.
Come on. I got you.
Hurry.
I got you. Come on.
Take my hand.
I got you. Here we go.
Go!
Hey. Are you all right?
- Here.
- Yeah.
What happened to your group?
I'm the only one left.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Let's get you out of here.
They took my son.
And I've been fighting them
ever since.
All we've managed to do so far
is contain them.
You can imagine
what would happen
if they made it
over that fence.
Like you can contain them.
People need to know
about this.
People
wouldn't even believe this.
People aren't ready
to know about this.
We've tried to protect him.
We've been working really hard
to keep it a secret.
But you have
to tell someone.
You've been searching
for the truth.
What do you do
when you find the truth?
Do you go
and you tell the people?
Or do you stay here
and fight this thing with us?
- Me?
- You're a survivor.
What do you survive for?
You can't possibly...
rationally believe
you can win this?
I believe we can.
I have to go back.
Arianne.
Good luck.
We're gonna need this.
Yeah.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org